David Zuñiga

San José, Costa Rica

+506 8327 4231 jdavid.zuniga.r@gmail.com www.spaceweb.dev

ABOUT ME

I would introduce myself in six words.

Passionate coder, responsible, best colleague ever. That pretty much sums it up, though at least the last one my former colleagues have to confirm. I try to do a good job in all roles I have in life, and I enjoy the process immensely. Do you want me to talk about my coding skills and experience now, or will we discuss it later in the interview?

COMPETENCIES

- Python
- SQL
- Google Cloud
- Airflow
- JavaScript
- Data Analytics
- · Cyber security
- Jenkins

LANGUAGES

- English, Full Professional Proficiency.
- · Spanish, Native.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IBM

- Technical Support Agent Apr 2019 to Nov 2019
- Backlog dispatcher lead: Manage L1 account backlog,
- Backlog data analysis using Python and reporting.
- Coordinate with different teams to work on new issues, priorities and special cases.
 - Centralize Technical Agent Nov 2019 to Feb 2021

Support to physical and virtual machines (Citrix) and servers (Azure and Google cloud) and configuration automation using Puppet.

 Backlog data analysis using service now, Python and MS Excel.

Server Engineer

Avid/CSS - February 2021 to Aug 2021

- Provide support to English speaking users on issues with Avid production management tools and their functionality on Windows and Linux servers.
- Log analysis, tasks automation with Python and management and automation with Terraform and Jenkins.

Cloud Automation Engineer

Equifax - Aug 2021 to present

- GCp and AWS task automation with Python, terraform, bash and data analysis with
- Google Big Query and, AirFlow

EDUCATION

CENFOTEC

- Infrastructure and IT superior technical degree.
- Front-end web Development Certification.
- ECCouncil Certified Ethical Hacker Certification.
- IT bachelor's degree.

Coursera

- IBM Cybersecurity Analyst Professional Certificate.
- Google IT Automation with Python Professional Certificate.
- Jenkins Automating your delivery pipeline.
- IBM AI Engineering Professional Certificate (Python).
- Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate.